杰 我该把这个处理掉吗
Jay, should I get rid of this?
帽子 夹克 还是手杖
The hat, the jacket, or the cane?
说实话 该扔 都该扔
Actually, yes. Just yes.
我们在办庭院大甩卖 以完成社会研究课的作业
We're having a yard sale for our social studies class
给联合国儿童基金会筹款
to raise money for UNICEF.
旨在让我们学习全球互相关爱的精神
The point is for us to learn about global altruism.
不对 是为了让我们的筹款
No, the point is for us
超过库珀老师的班级
to raise more money than Miss Cooper's class
那样我们就能吃披萨 开泳池派对了
so we get a pizza and a pool party.
你的玩世不恭让我忧国忧民
Your cynicism makes me sad for our world.
别紧张 迪尔加多 我明明见你很爱披萨的
Ease up, Delgado. I've seen you with a pizza.
我讨厌大甩卖
I hate garage sales.
成群的怪人组团来乱翻我的东西
Bunch of shady characters going through my stuff.
我直接写张支票不就行了吗
Why can't I just write a check?
放松点 杰
Relax, Jay.
不就那么几个人来我们家车道上嘛
It's just a couple of people in the driveway.
就是 就是 一开始是那样
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's where it starts.
然后就得寸进尺 "就打个本地电话嘛"
Then it's, "It's just a local call."
"能用下你家洗手间吗"
"Can I use your bathroom?"
"我妈妈得躺一下"
"My mother needs to lie down."
靠 太烦人了
No, it just stinks.
他确实给我写了张支票
He did write a check.
他知道得越少越好
The less he knows, the better.
你都不住这儿了
You're not even here anymore.
那也是我的东西
But it's my stuff.
妈妈呢 卢克 带我去妈那儿
Where's mom? Luke, take me to mom.
悠着点动弹 我昨晚喝多了...
And move slow. I'm still drunk
是喝多了咖啡 妈
-ing my coffee. Mom!
怎么了
What's the problem?
别让卢克卖我的东西
Tell Luke not to sell my stuff?
亲爱的 得了 算了吧
Honey, come on. Give it up.
约翰·梅尔本人都没有他自己的海报了
Even John Mayer doesn't have a John Mayer poster anymore.
他签了名的
It's signed by him.
跟你说实话吧 买的时候就有了
It's time you knew-- they come that way.
可是写着"致海莉"了呀
But it's "To Haley."
颜色不一样 那是你爸加上去的
In a different color. Your dad wrote that.
恶 他还写"我的身体是片仙境"
Ew! He wrote "my body is a wonderland."
他写了之后我才发现
I didn't catch that till after.
妈 迈克可以来参加大甩卖吗
Mom, is it okay if Michael comes to the yard sale?
亲爱的 你昨晚不是和他见过面了吗
Well, honey, didn't you see him last night?
所以呢 你为什么不喜欢我男朋友
So? Why don't you like my boyfriend?
我喜欢呀
I do like him.
我极度怀疑他可能是个同性恋
I'm just 90% sure he's 100% gay.
没错 迈克带我去舞会的时候
Yes, when Michael took me to prom,
我怀疑过他的性取向
I questioned his sexuality.
但是之后 我们亲热过
But then... we made out.
好几回了
A couple times.
甚至 掀起衣服 有肌肤之亲了
There was even a little... under-the-shirt action.
他的胸部手感可好了
His chest is very smooth.
小心 看车
Heads up! Coming through!
你终于要把那玩意处理掉了
I am glad you're finally getting rid of that thing.
说什么呢 我可不会卖我的宝贝
What? I'm not selling this bad boy.
我是想骑着这个去你爸家
I was gonna meet you at your dad's
顺便锻炼一下身体呢
and get a little exercise on the way.
你对我的阔步车有意见吗
What's,what's your beef with my streets rider?
我这个书呆子都觉得很呆气
Even I think it's nerdy, and I'm fluent in elvish.
一点都不呆 卢克 顶我一下
It's not nerdy. Luke, back me up.
你是说让我帮你顶进车库里吧
I hope you mean into the garage,
我在街上还有熟人呢
Because I have friends on this street.
亲爱的 你终于找到
Honey, you finally found something less cool
比双节裤更丢人的东西了
than those pants that zip off into shorts.
我的双节裤 买了以后你就一直吐槽
My shants, which you have been gunning for since day one.
你们难道就毫不关心
Does it matter to any of you
骑此车有利于心脑血管健康
that this is actually an extremely efficient cardiovascular workout
可以延长我的余生吗
that could prolong my life?
是啊 但那是怎样的余生呢 和谁一起过呢
Mm, yeah, but what kind of life? And with whom?
大家一定要记住哦 我们是在做慈善
Remember, everyone, this is for charity.
每一块钱都到能帮到一个患病儿童
Every dollar we earn helps a diseased child,
一个挨饿的儿童 和一个受虐的儿童
a starving child, an abused child.
大家购物开心
Now have fun!
说到挨饿儿童 我的捐赠来了
Speaking of starving children, here's my contribution.
6条大肥桶牛仔裤 我已经穿不上了
Six pair of jeans that don't fit me anymore
因为我减掉了25磅肉
Because I've lost 25 pounds.
大约是一二三个儿童保龄球的重量
That's like... one, two, three children's bowling balls.
-太棒了 -真不错
- Mm, bravo! - Very nice.
小卡
Hey, Cam?
你 你真的不要了吗
Are--are you really getting rid of all these?
你瞧 看上去都是崭新的呢
I mean, they're almost new. It's...
要是你...
Well, what if you, um--
要是我怎样啊 米奇尔 反弹吗
What if I what, Mitchell? Put the weight back on?
不 怎么会
No! No.
才不是呢 要是你
No, what if you--
万一你想到用牛仔裤进行什么艺术创作呢
You think of some creative art project that requires denim?
比如 以农场或者凯丽·克拉克森为主题的
You know, something farm or Kelly Clarkson-themed?
-或者 -我已经做过很多类似的主题了
- Or... - I've already done so much with that motif.
是啊 是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
不行 卖了 我要大清除[泻药]
You know what? No, sell 'em! I wanna purge,
声明一下 我可不是靠泻药减肥的
Which, for the record, is not how I lost this weight.
老是这样 他每次掉肉
Oh, every time. Every time he loses weight,
都把大号裤子扔了
he gets rid of his big pants.
体重反弹之后
And then when he puts the weight back on,
他又去买新裤子
he has to buy them all new again.
跟噩梦似的
It's--it's a nightmare.
趁他在屋子里 快把裤子放到车里
Just put the jeans in the car while he's in the house.
不行 爸爸 那简直太...
No, dad! That's incredibly dis--
好吧 就这么干
I'm gonna do that. Yeah.
你拿着这些裤子想去哪儿啊
Where you think you're going with those?
这些不卖
Oh, these aren't for sale.
我们是在做慈善呢
Hey, this is for charity.
你活生生地从那些急需帮助的
You know you're taking those jeans out of the hands
大胖墩儿童手里抢走了牛仔裤啊
of some needy, giant children.
你知道我们不是直接把牛仔裤捐出去吧 卢克
You know they're not getting the actual jeans, right, Luke?
噢 对哦 那就捐点钱吧
Oh. Right. Well, then how about a donation?
-20块 -100块
- 20 bucks? - 100.
是啊 你当然不在乎
Sure. What's it to you
那些非洲小孩在肮脏的大便河里洗澡得病了
if some kid gets sick bathing in poo river, Africa?
这个烟灰缸多少钱
How much for the ashtray?
不知道 标签上是多少钱
I don't know. What's the tag say?
50美分 但里头有个豁口
50 cents. But there's a chip in it.
所以我才把它放在草坪的毯子上
Well, that's why it's lying on a blanket on my lawn,
跟铁锥上的老玉米放一块儿
next to some old corn on the cob handles.
我只出35分
I'll give you 35.
你戴着价值一万块的手表
You're wearing a $10,000 watch.
却要为15分钱讨价还价吗
You're hagglig over 15 cents?
你住这么豪华的房子 便宜个15分都不行吗
You live in this place, and you can't let that 15 cents go?
好吧 35分
Fine. 35.
-你能找开50块钱吗 -滚远点
- Can you break a 50? - Get out.
曼尼
Manny.
这个箱子怎么在这里
What is this case doing here?
我在阁楼上找到的
I found it in the attic.
怎么了 里面装的什么
Why? What is it?
跟你没关系
Nothing that concerns you.
是我从哥伦比亚带来的
It's from Colombia.
-但我以为你说 -别胡思乱想
- But I thought you said-- - You thought nothing.
我要把它放回阁楼 不许再问问题
It's going back in the attic, and I want no more questions.
为什么
Why?
这也算是个问题
That's a question.
真诡异
That was weird.
太诡异了
Too weird.
我想知道里面有什么
I wonder what's in there.
醒醒吧 迪尔加多
Wake up, Delgado.
上锁的箱子 来自哥伦比亚
Locked box, from Colombia,
"不许问问题"
"No more questions"?
里面显然装着个人头
It's obviously a human head.
你为什么总是第一个就猜这个
Why is that always your first guess?
总有一天会证明我说的是对的
One of these days, I'm gonna be right.
不是吧
No way!
你要把这辆哈雷卖了吗
You're selling the Harley?
不是 我只是要把它移开而已
No, I'm just trying to move it out of the way.
有傻帽出价100块要买它
Some asshat offered me 100 bucks for it.
不过宝宝快出生了 我可能还是会卖掉
But with the baby coming, I guess I am gonna sell it.
真是辆好车
Oh, she's a beaut.
什么 你不会对它有兴趣吧
What, you wouldn't be interested in it, would you?
我为什么会没兴趣
Why wouldn't I be?
我只是觉得 你不太可能是摩托车发烧友
Well, I just never thought of you a motorcyle kinda guy.
如果克莱尔肯让我买一辆的话 我早就是了
I would be if Claire would ever let me have one.
你想要就买一辆呗
You can have a motorcycle if you want.
那我能跟我那超级性感的接待员来一炮吗
Can I also have an affair with my super hot receptionist?
什么超级性感的接待员
What super hot receptionist?
别转移话题
Don't change the subject!
大家午饭想吃什么
Now what would everybody like for lunch?
你要是不想要一辆摩托车 那就别买
You don't have to buy a motorcycle if you don't want one.
别怪罪到我头上 我又不介意
But don't blame it on me. I'm fine with it.
-真的吗 -真的
- Seriously? - Yeah.
当然了 我知道它虽然不太安全
Yeah, look, I know it's not the safest thing in the world,
但真的超性感
but it is sexy.
没错 比你骑的那奇葩机器要性感多了
Yes. A lot more sexy than that crazy machine you rode up on.
那是你医生强迫你骑着锻炼的吗
Is that something that your doctor make you use?
好了 我要把这车牵回去了
All right, I'm gonna take this around back,
除非你要试着骑骑看
unless you'd like to go for a test-drive.
当然了 走吧 不要太快哦
Sure. Let's go. Not too fast.
稀罕货
Precious cargo.
我可不载你 亲爱的
I'm not taking you, sweetheart.
让我自己开吗
I'm driving?
太赞了
Awesome!
我好怕好怕摩托车
I'm terrified of motorcycles,
但有时候你就得做点事儿来向世界证明
but sometimes you have to do things to show the world
你仍是个纯爷们
you're still a man.
所以我贴了个一次性纹身
Same reason I got that henna tattoo.
日文"勇气"
Japanese symbol for "Courage."
好的
Yeah.
迈克来了 你好啊迈克
Oh, Michael's here! Hi, Michael!
哟哟哟 这是哪一出
Well, well, well. What is this all about?
那是 那是艾丽克斯的新男友吗
Is there a-a new man in Alex's life?
她当然这样以为
Well, she certainly thinks so.
你看那家伙是直男吗
Is there any way that boy is straight?
怎么回事 我们这是在看谁呢
Ooh, what's going on? Who are we looking at?
那是艾丽克斯的新"男友"迈克
Uh, it's Alex's new "Boyfriend" Michael.
你打双引号是什么意思
What's up with the air quotes?
她觉得那家伙是同志
She thinks he's gay.
我"觉得"他是同志就跟
I "Think" he's gay the same way
我"觉得"这灯丑得吓人一样肯定
I "Think" that lamp is hideous.
好吧 我带来的 是我在艺术课上做的
Ok, brought it. Made it art class.
听着 我喜欢迈克 真的喜欢
Look, I like michael. I really do.
我只是 不希望她将来伤心
I just--I don't want her to get her heart broken.
一碰到男生
When it comes to boys,
她的自尊就几乎荡然无存
her self-esteem is low enough as it is.
不知道 艾丽克斯像是很坚强的人
I don't know. Alex seems pretty darn tough.
她只是表面上很刻薄
Oh, she's just sarcastic on the outside.
心里其实就是个脆弱的小女孩
Inside, she's just a fragile little girl.
你说那话的时候 干嘛看着我啊
By all means, look right at me when you say that.
就算她甘愿让同志伤她的心
If she wants to get her heart broken by a gay guy,
也得等到她18或19岁的时候才行
she can do so when she's 18 or 19
到时候她可以借酒消愁
and can drink her way through it.
哇 你真是个"好"妈妈
Aw. You're a "Good mother."
我也说不清 克莱尔 你有可能搞错了
I don't know, Claire. You could be wrong.
现在的男孩已经不在乎传统的男子气概那一套了
Boys aren't as concerned about traditional masculinity anymore.
他们不会故作强硬
You know, they're not butching it up.
他们不会压抑自己的感情
They're not pushing down their feelings.
-是啊 他们会很在乎着装 -嗯
- Yeah, they care about their clothes. - Mm-hmm.
-他们喜欢打扮 -嗯
- They--they--they groom. - Mm-hmm.
现在男人们都把汗毛刮得很干净
Everybody's hairless.
是啊 现在已经很难从外表分辨了
Yeah, you can't tell anything anymore.
是吗
Really?
米奇舅舅 小卡舅夫 这是迈克
Uncle Mitch, uncle Cam, this is Michael.
-嗨 -你好啊
- Hi! - Hello.
好了 快过来
Okay, come on.
-好吧 他是基佬无疑 -我们承认错误
- Yep, he's gay. - We stand corrected.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
小心点
Now be careful.
-我可不希望你撞车 -好感动
- I don't want you to crash. -Oh, oh.
-我不希望你把我的车撞散架了 -好吧
- I don't want the bike all scratched up. - Oh.
别紧张
And don't be nervous.
人一紧张就容易犯错
People make mistakes when they're nervous.
我才不紧张
I'm not nervous.
曾经我胯下的"雄物" 可比这大得多
I've had bigger hogs than this between my legs.
他真该说话前先过过脑子
He really oughta run things through his head first.
是啊
Yeah.
我知道我外表看上去酷毙了
I know I looked super cool on the outside,
但内心里 我怕得要死
But on the inside, I was terrified.
然后我想起
And then I remembered
方兹曾经在瞎眼的时候组装了一辆摩托车
that Fonzie once put together a whole motorcycle while blind.
然后我就想
And I thought,
那真是部好剧
That was a great show,
然后我就分散了注意力 一点都不害怕了
And I got really distracted and--and I forgot I was scared.
所以我向峡谷开去 将城市抛在脑后
So I headed up the canyon and I left the city behind.
我从未感到如此振奋
I'd never felt so exhilarated.
我不知道转变是何时发生的
I don't know exactly when it happened,
但在那条孤独之路上的某一刻
But somewhere on that lonely road...
车和人已经化为一体了
the bike and I became one.
噢 不
Ohh. Oh, no.
不 靠 你好重
No. Oh, you're heavy!
不 不要
No! Ohh!
把门锁上
Lock the door.
好吧 我们开干吧
Okay, let's do this.
不管我们在里面发现什么
No matter what we find in here,
我都会永远爱我妈
I will always love my mother.
即使里面是个人头吗
Even if it's a head?
肯定不是人头
It's not a head.
天啊 真是个人头
Oh, my god! It's a head!
我终于说对了
Ah! Finally!
米奇尔
Mitchell!
我刚刚在车那边 发现我的肥桶裤都在里面
I was just in the car, and I found my fat pants in there.
你知道是怎么回事吗
Do you know anything about that?
什么 不 是不是你忘了拿出来啊
What? No! No. Did you forget to put 'em out?
不 记得吗 我之前摆了姿势 人们鼓掌
No. Remember? I posed, people clapped. .
那一刻我可风光了
I had my moment
我现在想起来了
I do remember that.
那可真是"风光一刻"
That-- oh, that was a great moment.
我真为你骄傲
I am so proud of you.
怎么回事 你表现得怪怪的
What's going on? You're being weird.
怎么 你先说我是偷裤贼
What? First, I'm a pants thief
现在我夸奖一下你也不行吗
And--and now I can't pay you a compliment?
你知道谁才怪怪的吗 你
You know who's being weird? You.
克莱尔来了 嘿 姐们儿
Here comes Claire! Hey, girl!
我不知道你发什么神经
I don't know what that was.
好吧 我刚看到艾丽克斯和迈克坐在树上
Okay, I just saw Alex and Michael sittin' in a tree.
别逼我把什么都说出来
Don't make me spell this out for you.
你能怎么样呢
Well, what can you do?
我什么都干不了 但你们俩应该跟她谈谈
I can't do anything, but you two could talk to her.
告诉她什么
And tell her what?
迈克是"基佬队伍"中的一员
Michael's playing for the pink team.
好吧 我们可以自称基佬 你不能那么说
Okay, we get to say that. You don't really.
我知道 因为你们有可信度
I know, because you have credibility,
我说话她完全不会信的 我...
And I have the opposite of credibility. I have...
我是她妈
I am a mother.
我们才不会干的
Okay, we're not doing this.
-不会的 -稍等 稍等一下
- No. - Well, now hold on. Just a minute.
曾经 我还是个年少的小直男的时候
You know, when I was... young and straight,
我也曾伤过无数少女的芳心
I left a trail of broken hearts like a rock star.
我并不以此为荣
I'm not proud of it.
你挺以此为荣的
Ah, you're kinda proud of it.
你整天把这事儿挂在嘴上
You work it into a lot of conversations.
他昨天才刚说过
He brought it up yesterday.
好吧 我去了一家干洗店
Okay, how am I supposed to walk into a dry cleaner
怎么能不提我的女友温迪·乔·马丁纳斯
And not mention my girlfriend Wendy Jo Martinizer?
能继续说回到我的问题上吗
Can we get back to my problem?
你根本就没什么问题 他们只不过是孩子
You don't have a problem, okay? They're kids.
他们自己会解决的
They're gonna work it out.
你能跟她谈谈吗
Can you talk to her?
"他"现在这样我没法谈
Not when she's like this.
你是说艾丽克斯啊
Oh, you mean Alex.
好的 我去找她谈
Yeah. I'll do it.
谢谢
Thank you.
克莱尔 孩子们
Claire, kids,
如果你们看到这个 说明他们发现了我的尸体
If you're seeing this, then they found my body.
或者我总算等到一格信号 然后给你发了邮件
Or I finally got a signal and I sent it to you in an e-mail.
那样的话 我就直接给你打电话了 但是
In that case, I'll just call, but...
但有时候你可以接收到很强的
But sometimes you can actually get
数据传输信号 却不能进行语音通话
a pretty decent data signal and no voice.
我知道我在胡言乱语
I know I'm not making any sense.
我已经被困在这儿有...
I've been trapped out here now for...
27分钟了
27 minutes.
我太蠢了
I'm such an idiot.
我干嘛要把这该死的摩托车骑来这里
Why did I bring this stupid motorcycle out here?
就为了证明我是纯爷们吗
To prove I'm a man?
我就是个纯爷们
I am a man.
妈
Mom.
曼尼 你怎么会拿着这玩意
Manny, what's this doing here?
如果你不介意 我们要问你几个问题
If you don't mind, we'll be asking the questions now.
我介意
I do mind.
我很抱歉
I apologize.
我们没忍住好奇心
We couldn't help ourselves.
但我想知道
But I've gotta know.
你为什么要藏着这东西
Why were you hiding this?
好喜欢 我买了
Love this! Sold!
这背后有什么故事
What's the story here?
我不想谈这个
I don't want to talk about it!
真萌
Aw! Cute!
那小老头是哪里来的
Oh, where'd that come from?
是我妈妈的 但她遮遮掩掩
It's my mom's. She's being very cagey.
我们觉得她有事瞒着我们[头部藏毒品]
We think something's stashed in the head.
那可是从哥伦比亚带来的
It's from Colombia.
妈 有什么大不了的
Mom, what's the big deal?
好吧 我说
Okay, fine.
我年轻时 参加过一场选美比赛
When I was young, I was in a beauty pageant.
其他参赛的女孩们 在才艺秀环节
All the other girls, for their talent,
都一如既往地选择表演耍大刀
were juggling knives, as they always do.
但我想表现得与众不同
But I wanted to stand out,
所以我决定表演
so I came up with...
《臭脾气大叔》
Uncle Grumpy.
好吧 我从没如此激动过
Okay. Never been so happy.
不看完这一出我绝不走
Not leaving till I see it.
来吧 歌洛莉亚
Hit it, Gloria.
打扰一下 这个花瓶多少钱
Excuse me, how much is this vase?
给你了 拿走吧
It's yours. Take it.
你需要什么道具
So what do you need here?
大板凳 还是要喝水
A stool? Glass of water?
要怎么才能开始
How do we make this happen?
来吧 我要看
Let's go. I need to see this.
没什么可看的
You see nothing.
那次选美是我这辈子最糟糕的一晚
That pageant was one of the worst nights of my life.
我排练了好几个星期
After weeks of rehearsing,
但一上场就呆住了 我俩都说不出话来
I froze, and we were speechless.
结果你输了
Aw, and you lost.
不 我赢了
No. I won.
想象一下我18岁时的曼妙身姿
Imagine this when I was 18.
但那晚我太丢人了
But it was very humiliating.
我再也不想做那个表演了
I don't want to do it ever again.
但这么多年你还一直收藏着他
And yet, you kept him all these years.
也许你心里还是希望能重来一遍
Maybe there's a part of you that wants to work through this,
弥补当年的遗憾
get some closure.
你说的不对 陌生小哥
You're wrong, whoever you are.
已经过去31分钟了
It's going on 31 minutes.
感觉好寂寞
I feel so alone.
我得把腿挣脱出来
I gotta get my leg free.
我怎么没穿我的双节裤啊
Why didn't I wear my shants?!
伙计们 来看看
Hey, guys. Check it out.
喜欢我的新手镯吗
You like my new bracelet?
真好看
Ooh, cute.
迈克用那边一个旧窗帘环做的
It's an old curtain ring Michael saw over there.
他在上面编了三条皮鞋带
He braided three leather shoelaces around it
就做成了
And voila.
你知道吗 艾丽克斯 看到你和迈克
You know, Alex, you and Michael remind me so much
让我想起我和我的第一任女友
of me and my first girlfriend
安娜贝尔·皮卡特
Annabelle Pickett.
是吗 你还交过女朋友吗
Huh? You had a girlfriend?
是的 而且是主日学校的校花呢
Yeah. Cutest girl in Sunday school, too.
有一年 我邀请她一起参加
So one year, I asked her to go
教堂举办的《我爱记歌词》比赛
to the church bazaar lip sync contest with me,
表演了我们自己改编的《无尽的爱》
and we did our version of "Endless Love"...
说来很讽刺 因为两星期后
which was ironic because two weeks later,
我被一个名叫伍迪·雷的
I fell head over heels
年轻方下巴竞技场检票员迷得神魂颠倒
for a young square-jawed rodeo ticket taker named Woody Ray.
天呐
Oh, no.
可想而知 她心碎欲绝 痛不欲生
Of course, she was devastated, just destroyed her.
之后她用油漆在我爸爸的畜棚外
And then she spray-painted something unrepeatable
写上了非常难听的话
on my daddy's barn
然后再也没有理过我
and never spoke to me again.
哇 其实一切都是因为
Wow, and all because
她想强行把你掰成直男
she wanted you to be something you just weren't.
是的 没错
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
打住 我听明白了
Ugh. Stop. I get it.
我知道你心里怎么看迈克 妈
I know what you think about Michael, mom.
你没必要搬出你的基友恶势力来打压我
You didn't have to bring in your big gay guns to back you up.
无意冒犯
No offense.
-没关系 -我还挺爱听的
- None taken. - I kinda like it.
好吧 宝贝 我是为你担心
Okay. Honey, I am worried about you.
我不想让你受到伤害
I don't want you to get hurt.
我跟他们说过这是个馊主意 好吗
I told them that this was a bad idea, all right?
迈克也许是同志 也许不是
You know, maybe Michael's gay. Maybe he's not.
他肯定是
He is.
你妈妈只是想让你看清事实
Your mother just wants you to have all the information
这样你就能慢慢来
so that--that you can go slow.
米奇尔舅舅 他是直男
Uncle Mitchell, he's straight.
我们接吻了
We kissed.
天真的孩子 我...
Oh, honey, I...
我想做直男时 也和很多女孩接过吻
I kissed a lot of girls when I wanted to be straight.
你小卡舅夫也声称他亲过几个女孩
And your uncle cam kissed some, too, he says.
但那都不重要
But that's neither here nor there.
重要的是你要清楚自己的...你...
What's important is that you make your own--where--
等等 你要去哪里
Wait, where are you going?
你们那旧时代已经过去了
It's not the olden days anymore, you guys.
我直接问他就好
I can just ask him.
-这下你开心了吧 -才怪
- Hope you're happy. - I'm not.
"旧时代"三个字直接戳到我的痛处
That "Olden days" comment was like a punch to the gut.
她不如直接用喷漆喷在我爸的谷仓上呢
She may as well have spray-painted it on my daddy's barn.
我不管这事儿了
Yeah, I'm done with this.
他干嘛去
Where's he going?
嘿 你有面包吗
Hey, you got any bread?
我想确认下这个还能用不
I wanna make sure this thing till works.
少指望我来给你服务
Yeah, that' not gonna happen.
不一定非得是面包
Oh, it doesn't have to be bread.
我也可以用
I mean, I can get the information I need
面包圈或者冷冻的华夫饼来试
From, like, a bagel or a frozen waffle.
孩子 听好
Look, kid,
你不如掷色子听天由命吧
You're just gonna have to roll the dice on this one.
我不知道
I don't know.
退货规定是什么
What's your return policy?
你敢退货 我就报警
You return, I call the police.
你从哪儿拿的
Where'd you get that?
-从厨房 -那个不卖 给我拿来
- From the kitchen. - Give me that!
你的宠物猪卖吗
You selling the pot-bellied pig?
立刻从我眼前消失
Get out of my driveway.
你不是猪
You're not a pig.
你是爹地的乖女儿
You're daddy's little girl.
你在这儿呀
There you are.
嘿 抱歉
Hey. Sorry.
我看《艾尔装饰》看得入迷了
I got lost in this "Elle decor".
贾斯汀·汀布莱克正设计他的住宅
Justin Timberlake is designing his own home line,
我对此保留意见
and I'm trying to reserve judgment.
迈克 我要问你个事儿
Michael I have to ask you something.
我希望你明白 无论真实的你是怎样的都没关系
I want you to know it's okay either way.
但是...
But...
你是同志吗
Are you gay?
什么
What?
不 我不是
No! I'm not!
我 我的舞伴是你
I--I took you to prom.
我吻的也是你
I kissed you.
除非你是男孩 不然我绝对是直男
Unless you're a boy, I'm pretty sure I'm straight.
你是男孩吗
Are--are you a boy?
不是
No.
对嘛 所以我是直男
Right. So then I'm straight.
我没想惹你发火
I didn't mean to make you mad.
我没发火 我就是...
I'm not mad. I'm just...
愤怒
Angry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
其实那两个是同义词
And those are synonyms.
你就是无所不知是吧
You just know everything today.
让我一人待会儿行吗
Can you just give me a minute?
小哥 你坐这儿有何贵干[需要帮忙吗]
Hey, Can I help you?
需要 为什么大家都觉得我是同志
Yeah. Why does everybody think I'm gay?
老天 我恨大甩卖
God, I hate yard sales.
谢谢你
Thank you.
很抱歉乱翻 翻出了你的老头玩偶
Sorry for snooping around and finding your old man doll.
在哥伦比亚 如果你翻错了箱子
In colombia, if you snoop around the wrong box,
直接让你沉尸箱中
you might end up inside that box.
我知道我错了
I shouldn't have done it.
现在我挺替曼尼难过的
Now I feel bad for Manny.
什么意思
What do you mean?
该怎么说呢
Well, I don't know.
他总把你的勇敢挂在嘴边
He's always talking about how brave you are,
说你无所畏惧
how you're not afraid of anything.
现在他看起来有点失望
Now... he just seems a little sad.
有多失望
How sad?
别担心 这样挺好
Don't worry. It's a good thing.
他需要用现实来醒脑
He needs a little dose of reality.
在校园里
You walk around school,
到处跟人说自己妈有多棒
telling everyone how great your mommy is all the time,
最终只会让自己受伤疼痛
you find yourself on the business end of a wedgie.
我知道怎么用激将法得到我想要的
I know how to push buttons to get what I want.
我想要的是一场玩偶秀
And what I want is to see a puppet show.
我控诉
J'accuse!
不好意思 你说什么
I'm sorry. One more time?
只是用戏剧化的方式控诉你罢了
It's just a dramatic way of accusing you...
竟然把我的大码牛仔裤藏到灌木丛
Of stashing my fat pants in a bush!
-真会耍阴谋 -第二种控诉方式
- Saboteur! - That's a second way.
你...怎么...能够
How... could... you?
第三种
And a third.
为什么 米奇尔 为什么
Why, Mitchell? Why?
小卡 别这样
Cam... oh, come on.
好吧 其实...
All right, the...
我有点难以启齿 但是...
This is a little hard to say, but...
每次你丢掉这些大码裤子
Every time you get rid of these pants,
都会重新再买回来
You have to buy them all over again,
然后你会郁闷 明白吗
and you get depressed, all right?
我那么做只是为了留条后路
This is just a way to have a safety net.
我不能留后路 米奇尔
I can't have a safety net, Mitchell.
否则我无法减肥成功
Otherwise, I won't be successful and keep the weight off.
你就没想过那一点吗
Have you ever thought of that?
没有 我没想过
No. No, I didn't.
我跟你一样记得那些
You know, you're not the only one who remembers
减肥失败的惨痛经历
all the times I failed.
你说得对
You're right.
我应该更支持你才对 对不起
I--I should support you more. I'm--I'm sorry.
你能这么说我感到好幸福
I'm happy to hear you say that.
你幸福我就幸福
Well, I'm happy you're happy.
那么祝你俩幸福
Well, I hope you both are happy.
迈克不是同性恋 现在他恨死我了
Michael's not gay. Now he hates me.
真是多谢你们
Thanks a lot.
你看
You see?
就是因为这样 我才不想掺和这事儿
This is exactly why I didn't want to get involved.
我好难过
Now I feel terrible.
难过时吃馅饼再合适不过了
These feelings would go good with pie.
你回来啦
There he is!
亲爱的 喜欢吗
Sweetheart, do you love it?
不 克莱尔 我不喜欢
No, Claire, I do not love it.
太可惜了 车帅人俊 酷毙了
Oh, that's too bad 'cause you look so cool on that.
是吗 克莱尔 真的吗
Do I, Claire? Do I really?
发生什么事了
What happened?
说来话长 你自己看留言信箱吧
It's a long story. Check your in-box.
这么说吧 我不会买这辆摩托车的
But suffice it to say, I'm not buying that motorcycle.
-好 -我知道自己是谁 克莱尔
- Uh-huh. - I know what I am, Clare.
我不是摩托车手 我是"阔步车"手
I'm not a rider. I'm a strider.
希望这对你来说够性感
I hope that's sexy enough for you.
我的确看到了你性感的下半身
Well, I can see stuff.
我知道 我感觉有风吹过
Yeah, I know. I can feel air on it.
我又没有后备的裤子
It's not like I have another pair of pants.
今天你够幸运
Oh, uh, today is your lucky day.
都是为了慈善
It's for a good cause.
你可能需要皮带
You might need a belt.
不用吧 我想我们穿同一码
Oh, I doubt it. I bet we wear the same size.
少来这套
Don't do that.
明白
Copy.
顺便说下 我们毁了艾丽克斯的生活
Well, we ruined Alex's life, by the way.
还好吧 她挺好的
I don't know. She looks okay.
看起来他们和好了
Oh, looks like they made up.
如果她肯听我的话
If she would just listen to me,
我可以帮她避免好多心痛
I could help her avoid so much pain.
别插手她的事了 她才14岁
Give it a rest. She's 14, all right?
无论那个男生是谁 感情都不会长久的
No matter who that boy is, he's not gonna last.
你说得对
Mm, you're right.
至少和一个同志小哥在一起
Well, at leas with a gay kid,
他可以插花给她欣赏
you know she's gonna get a great flower arrangement.
你们应该瞧瞧我给安娜贝尔插的花
Should've seen the one I made Annabelle.
全是我亲手插的 美极了
Arranged it myself. It was gorgeous...
直到她把花拔出来 在我家门廊上拼出"基佬"字样
Till she pulled it apart and spelled "Homo" on my porch.
你这话对我没啥安慰作用
This doesn't make me feel any better.
大家过来吧
Gather around everybody.
我想给各位介绍一个人
I want you to meet somebody.
瞧这个我就开心了
Oh, but that might.
臭脾气大叔
Uncle Grumpy.
卢克的一番慧语让我顿悟
Luke's wise words got to me.
我要我的儿子再次尊敬我
I needed my son to respect me again.
不仅如此 我还需要重拾自尊
More than that, I needed to respect myself.
我滴个娘哦
Holy maracas!
我算是坐对大腿了
I think I sat on the right lap!
臭脾气大叔 我们在公众场合呢
Uncle Grumpy, we're in public.
瞧这些白种人
Ay, look at all those white faces!
看来我们是越境成功了
I see we made it over the wall.
臭脾气大叔 你心情不好吗
Uncle grumpy, are you in a bad mood?
他妈的说对了 我刚看完电影
Damn right I am! I just came from the movies.
一天工资全买票看《本能》了
A whole day's pay to see "Basic instinct."
你觉得怎么样
Oh. And what did you think?
基"本"上 很烂[能]
Basically, it stinked.
你脾气太臭了
You're so grumpy.
他妈的说对了
Damn right I am!
我刚碰到了我的梦中情人
I just met the girl of my dreams.
真是太好了
Ay, that's such great news.
才怪 她把白蚁传染给了我
No. She gave me the termites.
歌洛莉亚 我打算...
Gloria, I'm just gonna--
老天 我连知道的兴趣都没有
Oh, jeez. I don't even wanna know what this is.
我走了
I'm outta here.
-你要出去吗 -他妈的说对了
- You're leaving? - Damn right.
大甩卖和"擅闯民宅"的唯一区别在于
The only difference between this and a home invasion
我可以冲擅闯民宅的人开枪
is I get to shoot people at a home invasion.
我的天 她嫁的人跟她的木偶一样
Oh, my god. She married her puppet.
臭脾气大叔
Uncle Grumpy!
有人听到吗
Can anyone hear me?!
救命啊
Please help me!
我不想死啊
I don't wanna die!
如果我必须弄个歌曲播放列表
If I had to make a playlist
用于困在摩托车下时听的话
for being trapped under a motorcycle,
会有
It'd be, um...
《无法动弹》 《上路吧 杰克》
"Stuck in the middle," "Hit the road Jack,"
重炮D唱的随便什么歌
Um, anything by Heavy D.
指针姐妹的《困兽之舞》
Ooh, Pointer sisters, "Neutron dance."
原来 今天不是
Turns out today wasn't
我未来人生的崭新一页
the first day of the rest of my life.
我的天
Oh, my goodness.
我衣柜里有个鞋盒里面有些DVD
There's some DVDs in a shoe box in, uh,my closet
那是一哥们儿放我家暂存的
that I was holding for... a buddy.
直接把盒子扔掉就行了
Um, you can go ahead and just throw the whole box away.
我好饿
I'm so hungry.
不知道要在这里困多久
I don't know how long I'm gonna be out here.
我得吃点保命的粮食了
I gotta ration my food.
我说了不要加番茄的
I said no tomatoes!